Yes, we've started live transmission.
It's started? Cheer up.
Let's go.
It's the 8th of May, in real time.
Yes, it's early.
It's early, isn't it? Shut up!
I don't want to be told by you. Don't talk, don't breathe.
It's already started.
The whole world is running.
It's not good.
This show is power harassment!
They think we're harassing them, so we'll be fine.
In the eyes of the public.
It's a no-no.
Let's get started!
We'll start recording again.
Please open the door so we can start recording again.
Please open the door.
Five seconds.
Four.
Three.
Well, um, I ate.
I ate it.
That Bean-curd soup with red pepper paste
I ate
The spicy one.
Wasn't it good?
It was good, but...
But as expected, the moment you first put it in your mouth...
I felt something like, oh, oh, oh, oh...
I felt the chilli.
Chilli, yes.
It definitely goes with rice, doesn't it?
And it was just time for lunch.
I put a little bit of that on top of the rice.
I was allowed to eat it.
I wasn't hungry.
Oh, my God, you haven't eaten yet? I didn't eat it, I ate it, because I wasn't hungry.
I haven't eaten yet.
I'm quite full from the hot bean curd.
About a block of tofu.
Maybe.
The staff...
It was a small portion.
That's what you guys ate.
That's a lot of food.
It was a small portion, but it was delicious.
It was a big portion.
But it was delicious.
But it was good.
Spicy!
I've been really into hot bean curd lately.
It's really spicy.
You're still chattering.
It was delicious.
That was a fast meal.
It's amazing how fast you can eat spicy food.
Hey!
Did you eat? Yes, I ate it. I had it.
It's delicious!
It was a bit spicy.
Oh, no, no, no, I thought it was great.
Anyway, it had a powerful enemy.
Once again, it was delicious.
So, first of all...
Let's say a few words of wisdom.
Yes, this way, I think.
Do you know Edo Sheeran? I know. He's a four-time Grammy Award winner.
I've got a quick look. FGFG.
Wait a minute.
Isn't it floating?
If you look at Asayuki's photo, it looks like this.
91, right? I'm 97.
The Rokkoya guy isn't this flabby.
No, it was something like this.
Ed Sheeran said... he's not this old... but he looked like this...
Hade Sheeran said...
I don't know...
It's a distribution thing.
It's got 3.64 billion views.
Shape of You.
Oh, you know.
Like, the song Tentente. - I can't say what it is, but the key to failure is trying to please everybody.
I see.
You mean you don't have to please everyone, but you do have to have a small fan base.
That's right.
I think that's a great quote.
I'm the complete opposite.
If I'm left to my own devices, I tend to get caught up in my own originality.
I think, "Wait a minute, is this something that everyone who sees this will like?
Oh!
So it's the opposite.
I see.
What is Edo?
What is Edo, my friend?
What?
Edo?
Edo. Edo.
But surely you've seen your own merchandise, Edo's, Edo? But surely you can do that with your own merchandise? But surely you're doing it with your own merchandise.
Edo no...
That's how much he loves it.
He's a very interesting person, isn't he?
Yes, he is.
When you look at all the things he does...
He's... well, I don't know...
I don't know, she's... a little too human in appearance.
No, no, I don't mean it's not human.
She looks a bit like a god, doesn't she?
But the atmosphere...
She has an aura about her.
Even in pictures.
Yes, you're right.
There's an aura of warmth about you, isn't there?
That's why.
And now...
This...
I'm going to go.
I was born in Suwa, Nagano Prefecture, where there's a lake called Suwa Lake,
The lake was created by a meteorite that fell there in the movie Your Name.
The lake was modeled after Lake Suwa in Kimi no Namae, where a meteorite fell and created a lake,
The lake was created by a meteorite that fell and formed a lake.
Yes, there is.
I think that's probably where you are, and that's why Mr Hidibi-san, who is famous amongst fans, is from Asagashima, Saitama Prefecture.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to take 10 consecutive Golden Week holidays.
Because I thought I'd take a very long time this year.
That's right.
I've travelled to Toyama, Ishikawa, Fukui, Gifu and Nagano!
I'm talking a lot!
I saw a lot of amazing scenery.
This time, I went to a place called Takagubi Kogen in Nagano.
The famous Shiojiri, or is it around there?
Subayuri, a little further up the mountain.
The view from the highland is exactly like the one in
That's what your name is in the movie.
By the way, he took this photo of the night view, but do you recognize it?
Yes, this is it.
Well, you know... he told me that this is really the place.
The night view is amazing.
The city of Suwa, Okaya, Shimosuwa, etc.
The city of Suwa, Okaya, Shimo-Suwa and Suwa Lake.
This is Suwa Lake.
I'm a big fan of the Suwa River.
I'm going to go to the Suwa River.
It's pretty nice. I want to go there. I want to see the nature.
You can do anything you want. And the Kinkakuji Temple, which has been the talk of the town lately.
Thank you.
She went to the Golden Pavilion for the first time in 22 years with her husband.
This is it.
Kinkaku-ji is nice.
He's been talking about it a lot lately.
That's right.
I think it's really gold.
It really is gold.
And it's bigger than I thought.
Yes, it is.
It's a rare pattern that the real thing is bigger.
It's a bit smaller than it looks in the textbooks.
I thought it'd be more personalised.
I'm really surprised at how big it is.
That's what I really think.
Okay, so...
This pond in front of the Golden Pavilion is also nice.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
You want to take a picture with it, for sure.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Also, in this series...
Yes.
Sirene.
Thank you, Mishima City, Shizuoka Prefecture,
You mean the bush cherry?
I know, the cherry blossoms under there.
Where is it now? Somewhere...
It's more famous in Chichibu.
I see.
You're a local, aren't you, Shiranu?
I'm from Mishima City, Shizuoka Prefecture,
I went to the Fuji-Shiba Cherry Blossom Festival!
I saw that poster!
That's what it's all about.
I saw it!
It's beautiful!
These so-called cherry blossoms...
The flowers bloom like a carpet.
Wow, two Mt Fuji's.
This isn't natural, is it?
Yeah, this is probably...
This was made...
Fuji.
I see.
The park made this.
Little Fuji.
It's kind of cute.
It's so squat and beautiful.
That's nice.
Wow, there's a place like this.
I've never heard of it.
You can see Mount Fuji from here.
Fuji, so I think it's somewhere in Shizuoka or there.
There's also a place in the Kanto region, around Chichibu in Saitama, that's really famous for its bush cherry blossoms, and it's pink all over.
It's like, wow, is this for real?
So this is exactly the season for me.
The bush cherry blossoms are a bit late.
I saw them last year in Yamagata and other places.
I don't know...
Memophila is also at this time of year, isn't it?
Blue and pink.
It's lovely, this time of year.
Yes, during Golden Week.
Ibaraki.
I'm going to be in Ibaraki for the Ibaraki Robots basketball team's halftime show.
For the Ibaraki Robots basketball team's halftime show.
I went to Ibaraki for the halftime show.
I went to Ibaraki to do a halftime show for the Ibaraki Robots basketball team.
Golden Week and all that.
There was a hell of a lot of traffic!
Yeah!
It took me three and a half hours to get home.
Yeah, I heard it was particularly congested this year.
What did you do during Golden Week? That's what I was doing.
You got stuck in traffic.
You did have a good Golden Week, didn't you?
All those tourist attractions...
Of course, with the Corona disaster... it's the first time this year, I guess.
But there were already a lot of people.
But it's good that you're a businessman.
That's right.
That's why I didn't do anything special during Golden Week.
Really?
I just came to work and did my normal job.
What?
I see.
No change at all.
What?
Oh, I see.
I see.
No change at all.
It's always the same, isn't it?
But on the other hand... it's nice to be able to rest at different times with different people, with different people.
Well, well, well, well.
It's better to be off.
It's better to be off at different times from everyone else, because there are fewer people.
No, I'm done.
Can we just carry on like this?
Well...
Shall we close the show?
Shall we close it once?
Well, let's...
This block...
I'd like to tighten it once.
Why did you reduce it so much? Master.
I knew it. Speaking of closing, I'm known as the closing girl.
You can close one if you want.
I've never heard that before.
That's right.
You can always close the one you want at every important juncture.
But sure.
Well, here's one.
What, here?
Well, that's it for today! Yo!
Don't open it!
Are you sure? Are you sure it's over?
Wait a minute.
What is it?
Master, what's the date today?
Today?
In real time, I mean.
Yes, that's right.
Is there any day that's closer?
Isn't it my birthday?
What's that? They don't ring much.
Hey, hey, hey.
Just a little bit, not much.
Not much ringing.
Ring it.
Master, say it again.
Isn't it my birthday?
Whoa.
It's so small.
That's the best I can do.
I'll edit it out.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
It's Master's birthday.
Thank you very much.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, Master.
So...
How old are you?
Fifty-eight.
Wow.
That's cool.
Hinoyama's 54.
Fifty-eight?
Not even close.
I'm younger.
When I say birthday...
presents, right?
I've got it for you.
I've done it.
It's been a while.
You want me to go get it?
It's coming.
Something's here.
Thank you, I'll go get it too.
I'm going to get it, too.
I'll start with you, Master.
Oh, my God! What's this?
This way.
Baccarat!
Master, you drink a lot of oolong tea, don't you?
Yes, I do.
So, I'd like to buy you some nice glasses.
Can I drink oolong tea in a Baccarat glass?
No, I'd like you to try some.
Wait, no!
Oh, my God. - Like a Kakarot.
Baccarat.
There's a lot of baccarat out there.
Well, then...
Oh, wow.
Baccarat!
It's exactly like Baccarat.
It's a bit thick.
I'm scared of the way you hold it.
Why do you hold it like that?
It's so massive, it's scary, scary, scary? It's so massive.
Scary, scary, scary.
It's so massive, isn't it?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Please come in with this, Oolong.
It's heavy.
Can I have it?
Why the fuck not?
Look how well it matches the colour.
They match.
And the red.
That's why I asked for it.
I said, "So give it to me because I'm an idiot.
Give it to me because I'm an idiot.
Why is this a new kind of mugging?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Thank you very much.
I'll just pack it up.
Congratulations, 58.
The Oolong Cup.
I see... 18 years old and a cup of oolong for me.
I see.
I'll start with...
This is the first one from all of you.
Thank you very much.
Okay, I'll just...
Can I open it?
I don't know...
I'll go first.
It's early.
When you're done...
Oh!
What's this?
Tangle Teezer
For combing hair.
Yes, yes, yes.
I know, I know, I know.
Tangle Tee-zah, yes, that amazing thing, right?
How about this?
Hold on, hold on.
mmm...
It's a T that turns.
It looks like it's going to break.
Here, like this.
But before this.
Before?
Before.
Before you melt it.
Put this oil here.
I put a little bit of this oil on the paper.
It makes it easier to set.
I see.
This is Refa oil.
It's called "lock oil" and if you put it in your hair before curling or straightening it, it will keep it in place all day and protect it from humidity.
It keeps it in place all day and protects it from humidity, so it doesn't spread.
It's true, I don't put anything on my hair, all the time.
I don't even use a blow-dryer. It's really good if you put it on your name or something.
I don't put it on my hair, I don't use a blow-dryer or anything, it's really good.
I've seen this logo before.
Yes, I can see it.
You can wear shox too, if you like.
Thank you.
I'd like to have some of this brand.
Oh, my God, is it in one of these?
Look at this.
It's got a zip.
It's in a pouch, so you can take it with you if you want.
It's really like a Ginza Millenie's.
It's like that.
Ginza Millenies sounds really cheap, but that's the name.
Please use it if you like.
Thank you.
It's true.
It's in the case.
You can use this case too.
I'll put it in this so you can use it.
Wow.
Then you can wear them.
Thank you very much.
Well, well, well.
What a surprise from the show.
Thank you very much.
Try it in the morning.
What the hell?
What's this?
It's amazing!
Yamagata cherries.
I want some!
Red Akiu.
Cherries?
Are those the high-end, high-end cherries? Wow! Those expensive...
Luxury cherries?
Oh, my God.
That's amazing.
That's nice.
Let's have a look.
Isn't it too stylish?
It is, isn't it?
Yamagata already has cherry blossoms.
Oh, duh-duh-duh.
Wow!
Look at the cherry tomatoes!
The grains are beautiful.
Cute.
Wow!
Greenhouse!
Greenhouse-grown!
So beautiful!
So shiny!
Absolutely delicious! Oh, my God!
I've never seen them like this before.
It's so good!
Would you like to try some?
Yes, yes, yes.
Let's eat.
You don't mind?
Yes! You've eaten and eaten.
Adasa.
I've grown up with cherries since I was a child. I want some of those, too, but they're from Yamagata.
Oh, I see. The sample was full of them, too.
There really are a lot of cherry farmers in Yamagata, and there's a surprisingly large amount of cherries.
I see.
There are also a lot of people whose last name is Sato.
There are a lot of Sato's too.
Sato from Sato Bishiki.
Can I ask you to open it?
Wow!
But, you know, I'm also getting a huge devil's charge.
Thank you.
I'll read as much as I can.
Ah, Mr. Kahikaho.
I have your Oyelon Tile Ice Table.
Ice stand.
That's very thoughtful of you.
Congratulations on your mastery, M Nagaoka-san.
And Mr Takuminchi.
Congratulations on the Master's tan play presentation ceremony.
Thank you, Takuminchi!
Congratulations to Tamami-san, Master of the Onpure presentation ceremony, and congratulations to Tamami-san, Master of the Takumi family.
And Sukutsukumo Shiki-san, congratulations to you!
Congratulations to Momoshiki-san, only two more years to go till "Nee"!
Two more years to go till I'll be a star and a good man of Zadar, please keep good health in the future, okay?
I've already talked about their faces, but I really know their names, right?
Like we used to go to school together.
Like that? Like old friends.
Like classmates from high school.
Like we're friends in high school.
Thank you very much. Thank you very much.
So, please, come in.
Master to Master, Master to Master, may I?
Oh, wow.
That's a big one.
It's huge.
Huge.
Big!
It's amazing.
It's shiny.
Cute.
May I?
Thank you very much.
How is it?
It's good.
Really, really good. Sweet, I'll take it.
You can have it, but thank you. It's so rich, it tastes so rich.
Cherry blossoms are cute, but so are the ones you want.
Thank you, guys.
I'll see you soon.
It's thick.
It's got a lot of flavor.
This is delicious!
The meat feels really firm.
Whoever chose this has good taste.
I've never had a cherry blossom like this.
It's delicious.
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Please, I'll make you another batch.
Yes!
I can't stop eating them.
Congratulations to General Red Cyclone.
I got a lot of comments about it.
They're delicious.
I want one!
I want one...
I'm really happy for you.
What kind of year do you want it to be? Well, rather than what kind of year, I'd say...
What kind of year do you want it to be?
What kind of year do you want to have?
Well, you know...
It's a year anyway, but...
Tomorrow...
And the day after tomorrow.
I want to make tomorrow better than today, and the day after tomorrow better than the day after tomorrow.
I'd like to make it a GD one.
Please continue to give me your guidance and your news.
I'm not listening to the waves of your guidance and news.
Thank you very much for today.
That's great.
Congratulations.
Cheers.
Thank you very much.
Baccarat.リ